itpro.tv 2019-03-31

# Privacy | Protecting your privacy on ITProTV

At ITProTV, we value the privacy and security of your personal information, and are committed to the fair and transparent processing of your information. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect, why we collect it, and how you can update, manage and delete your information.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We collect only the personal information1 that we need in order to provide you with the products or services that you order. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Upon written request, we will disclose to you the personal information we hold about you, and will endeavor, to the extent technically feasible, to delete or render inaccessible your personal information. You may also request that we correct or amend such personal information so that any inaccurate or incomplete personal information can be corrected or completed without undue delay. Such requests should be directed to our Director of Privacy, whose contact information is provided below.

We will endeavor to respond to your requests to view, correct or delete your personal information without undue delay, or within approximately one month following verification of your identity. Note that we will undertake a good faith effort to accommodate requests for access to or deletion of personal information. However, these requests may be subject to an evaluation of additional factors, including disproportionate burden or expense, or the risk to the privacy or other rights of others. We may also retain and use your personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our rights or agreements, and for other lawful business purposes.

1The term personal information, as used in this Privacy Policy, includes “personal data” as defined by the General Data Protection Regulation, “personal information” or “personally identifiable information” as defined in various United States data breach notification laws and information that may otherwise be used to identify an individual. 

## How do we use your information?

Any of the information we collect from you will only be used to process your order with us and to provide you with informational material relating to other of our products and services that may be of interest to you. However, you have the right to opt out of receiving these additional materials.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of technical and organizational security measures to maintain the safety, integrity and confidentiality of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider’s database so that it is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, who have a role in providing adequate protection to your information.

After a transaction is processed, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. We may provide certain of your information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties provide us assurances that they will provide adequate protection to your information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect yours, ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. We do not edit, review or make decisions concerning information you decide to share with others on our site, including, but not limited to, any personal information.

## Links to sites of third parties

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we encourage you to review before inputting any personal information into those sites. However, we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘My Profile’ page.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

Because we take the privacy and security of your information very seriously, including our subscribers who reside in the European Union, we are committed to protecting your personal information in accordance with provisions of the GDPR. We are building privacy and security of personal information into our technical and organizational systems and processes related to any personal information we process. We do not sell, exchange or transfer member information for any reason, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested. The personal information we collect is limited to that which is necessary to provide the products and services you request, and your information is only kept as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [ https://www.itpro.tv/eula/](https://itpro.tv/eula/).

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update, modify or change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We always indicate the date the last updates were published. This policy was last modified on May 25, 2018. If the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact our Director of Privacy at [dpo@itpro.tv](mailto:dpo@itpro.tv). You may also contact us using the information below:
